Guide to the Lee Felsenstein Papers M1443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: LGC Engineering
  - Subseries 4.4: Business Records
    - VDM-II software specification, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - VDM-II Sales, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Glitch City, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Invoices, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - ETRA History, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - ETRA, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - LGC Schematics, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Video Modular Systems (VMS), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - PTCO Designs notebook, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - LGC Designs notebook, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Articles, schematics, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - SYS-013 Pipeline Receiver, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lambda-Instruction Manuals, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Power Wiring, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - VMP, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Schematics, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - S-100, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Cruncher, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Pertec 1000 + form, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Schematics, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - LGC account-paid bills, May 1980 - Aug. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - LGC account-paid bills, Sep. 1980 - Dec. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Golemics Construction Account-paid bills, May 1980 - Sep. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Golemics Construction Account-paid bills, Sep. 1980 - Dec. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - LGC account-paid bills, Jan. 1980 - Apr. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Invoices, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - LGC Receipts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - All 1978 Receipts for Non-Deductable Items (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - LGC Receipts, Jan. 1978 - Apr. 1978 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - LGC Receipts, May 1978 - Aug. 1978 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - LGC Receipts, Sep. 1978 - Dec. 1978 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Weekly Time Sheets, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Golemics Receipts, Jan. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Golemics Receipts, Feb. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Golemics Receipts, Mar. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Golemics Receipts, Apr. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Golemics Receipts, May 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Golemics Receipts, June 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Golemics Receipts, Jul. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Golemics Receipts, Aug. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Golemics Receipts, Sep. 1979 - Dec. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Golemics Construction-checks, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - LGC check receipts, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
    - LGC check receipts, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - LGC check receipts, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - LGC check receipts, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - LGC deposits, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - LGC bank statements, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - LGC bank statements, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - LGC Pacific Gas and Electric bills, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - LGC accounts receivables, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - LGC statements, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - LGC form masters, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - LGC accounts receivables, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - LGC accounts receivables A-K, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - LGC accounts receivables L-Z, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - LGC accounts receivables A-K, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - LGC accounts receivables L-Z, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - LGC deposits, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - LGC bank statements, 1980-1982, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - LGC tax forms, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Caitlin's stuff, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Library Listing, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - LGC financial data, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Space/Area Use Plans, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Fictitious Business Name Information, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Schwabacher-Frey paid invoices, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Red Alarm security contract, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Janitorial Info, Fire Extinguisher, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Copier Use Log, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Credit Applications, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - LGC paid bills, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - LGC utilities, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - LGC invoices and receipts, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Terminix Pest Killers, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Lease, Rent Information, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Paid Bills, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Utilities, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Subscription Information, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - LGC Personnel, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - LGC Ledgers, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - LGC Ledgers, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - LGC Receipts, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - LGC purchase orders, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - LGC miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - LGC loans, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Materials In/Out, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - California Software Research and Development, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Documentation Management, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Sequitur Comparison, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - 1987 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Subseries 4.5: Schematics
    - Early LGC-Astral, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Early LGC-Burst Generator, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Early LGC-Cluster Terminal, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Early LGC-[schematics, Doppler radar article], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Early LGC-Sinus, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Early LGC-Diablo Hytype Interface, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Early LGC-schematics, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Early LGC-NASA, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Early LGC-Tom Swift specifications, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Early LGC-[computer club correspondence, newsletters], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Early LGC-SOL, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Early LGC-[correspondence, newsletters, articles], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Early LGC-TEC, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Early LGC-Horizontal Tab, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Computation Notebook, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Series 5: Osborne Computer Corporation
  - Osborne, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lee Felsenstein's letters to Osborne personnel during his tenure, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Osborne Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Osborne-Jim Ottinger, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Osborne-Adam Osborne, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
  - Osborne Computer Corporation Approved Software, 1981 - 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    contains 5-1/4 floppy disks: Enumerator; Personal Datebook
  - Osborne Computer Corporation Approved Software: Money Maestro; Microlink, 1981 - 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Osborne Computer Corporation Approved Software: Double Density; System Checker; Comm-Pac, 1981 - 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Osborne-Start Pac Quick Start Self Instruction System (Box 35, Folder 7)
    contains audio cassette tapes
- Series 6: Village Design
  - Subseries 6.1: Correspondence
    - VD Letterhead (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Johnson-Lenz, 1977 - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Community Memory Correspondence, 1979 - 1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Embosser that marks, Village Design-Incorporated, 06-08-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Stainless steel embosser
  - Subseries 6.2: Publications
    - Village One, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Misc Small Farm Stuff, 1979 - 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Blackberry Services, Inc. Eugene Oregon, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin Boards Court Cases, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Resource One Newsletter No. 2, Apr. 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Guide for Using the Community Memory, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - CM: Public Info Network (original), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Vallee, Jacques et al The Computer Conference: An Altered State of Communication, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Community Memory essays, 1976 - 1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Network Proposal (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Worker Manual Rogers CM (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Writeups-R/O-CM, 1973 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Infact/Community Memory Writeups from III.2 Futures Conditional (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - CDC, 1979 - 1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Connections: a curriculum in appropriate technology for 5th and 6th grades, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Rand, George et al Research Agenda: Coming to Terms with the Environment's Future (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Wynn (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Office of the Future, 1979 - 1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Nyborg, Philip S. Regulatory inhibitions on the development of electronic message systems in the USA, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Legal Implications, 1979 - 1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Village Design Background Papers, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Journal of the Bay Tea Company, Jan. 1974 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - An Example Dialogue with the Proposed Community Memory System (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Radio KILI Terre Beynart (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Critique of Community Communications Brian Kirk (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Audio Conferencing Karen Paulsell, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Home Sweet Marketplace Vincent Mosco (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Messianic Expectations Pat Wagner (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - In Progress, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - JCC-Next ISHU, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Public Interest Computer Association, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - RAIN, 1982 - 1983 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - SF Neighborhood Organizations Misc, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Technology and Society Committee and Teleguide, 1983 - 1984 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Union of Democratic Communications, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - VDT Newsletter and VDTS Info, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Subseries 6.3: Promotional Materials
    - KILI Radio, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Campbell, Duncan "The Global Boom in Eavesdropping", 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6.4: Manuals
    - Check Receipts, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Check Receipts, 1978 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Check Receipts, 1982 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Check Receipts, 1978 - 1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Franchise (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Donations VD, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Receipts for Donations VD, 1980 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Donations per Judith Adell, 12-17-1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - VD Donor Info/Tax, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Bombs Away/VD, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - The Source, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Phone Bills-VD, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - UNIX Acct, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Pacific Software/First United Thrift and Loan Equipment lease, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Golemics PacSoftware, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Osborne Stock Filings, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Golemics M. Montgomery Separations, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Golemics Stock Sale, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Golemics Rioch, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Up Right-Golemics, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Golemics Upstart, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Golemics BLI Contract, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Golemics Promissory Notes, 1982 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Golemics, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Golemics, Inc. Agreements 00161, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Case No. 00161 Golemics/Osborne Stk Sale, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - VD Liability Insurance, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sklar, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Perkins, Carolyn re: AB699, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Singsen (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - CM Design, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Tom Swift Terminal, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - CM History, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Resource One (mostly historical), 1972 - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Festival/Directory Proposal (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Village Design Bank Stuff (ancient), 1976 - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Financial Worksheets VD, 1977 - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Proposal for a Cooperative Computer Services and Community Information System (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Stanford, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Village Design Cancelled Checks, 1984 - 1985 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Village Design 1985 Check Register + Cash Receipts (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Village Design Income + Expense Statements, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - VD Tax 1984 Payroll (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Central Bank Village Design, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - VD Central Bank, 1980 - 1984 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Old checks and desposit slips, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Village Design Business, 1976 - 1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Village Design Ledgers, 1978 - 1981 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Village Design Ledgers, 1982 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Village Design Records, 1982 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Journal of Community Communications-Copyright Registration, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Originals of printed forms, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - United Way, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Village Design-By Laws, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Village Design-Postal Permit, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Village Design-Federal Exemption, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Village Design-California Franchise Tax Board, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Village Design-state CT-2 forms, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Village Design-employer identification number, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Village Design-good copies of financial history and operating budget, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Village Design-Registry of Charitable Trusts, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Village Design-statements for taxes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Village Design-taxes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Village Design-franchise tax board, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Village Design-meeting, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Village Design-Central Bank, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Village Design-990 tax forms, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Village Design-donations, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Village Design-meetings, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Village Design-invoices, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Village Design-meetings, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Village Design-business records, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Village Design-business records, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Village Design-meetings, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Village Design-business records, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Village Design-business records, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Village Design-meetings, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Village Design-business records, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Village Design-members, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Village Design-business records, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Village Design-business records, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Village Design-meetings, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Village Design-business records, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Village Design-business records, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Village Design-business records, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Village Design-business records, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Village Design-business records, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Graphics [clippings] (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Series 7: Upstart Corporation
  - Subseries 7.1: Invoices
    - Upstart/Colorblind PPC Invoice, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 7.2: Financial Statements
    - Financial-Upstart (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Subseries 7.3: Promotional Materials
    - Upstart/Colorblind Packaging, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Upstart Corporation direct mail info, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Colorblind-Marketing/Sales, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Upstart Corporation Product Endorsements, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 7.4: Business Records
    - Design-Main Board, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Integrated Circuit Specifications (IC Specs)-80386, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Integrated Circuit Specifications (IC Specs)-SIP RAM, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Integrated Circuit Specifications (IC Specs)-PL Osc, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Integrated Circuit Specifications (IC Specs)-PALs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Integrated Circuit Specifications (IC Specs)-ROMs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Video Interface, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Ricoh Products, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Manufacturers' Ads (printers, copiers), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - GVO, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - U.S. Pixel Specifications, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Various Manufacturers' Product Specifications, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 48-49)
    - Moniterm, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Job 105, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Schematics, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - 116-contract, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Subroutines article (mentions Felsenstein), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Mechanical specifications, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Software advisory committee / correspondence, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Phoenix Technologies, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Patents, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
    - PC Layout Quotes (HV Design), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Upstart Corp-Non-Disclosure Agreements, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 116-schedule and budget, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Specification Hardware, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Specification Software, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Software-Unix, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 116-Preliminary Specifications, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 116-Descriptions, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Design-IO, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Design-Program Memory, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Monochrome Alpha / Graphics, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Design D-Memory, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Assembly, Top #116000 N/A, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Assembly, I/O #116001 N/A: 116000, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Assembly, I/O Case #116002 N/A: 116001, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Assembly, I/O PC #116003 N/A: 116001, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Fabrication, I/O PC #116004 N/A: 116003, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Schematics, I/O PC #116005 N/A: 116003, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Assembly, I/O Cable #116006 N/A: 116000, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Schematics, I/O Cable #116007 N/A: 116006, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Assembly, Main PC #116008 N/A: 116000, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Fabrication, PC, Main Board Proto #116010 N/A: 116009, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Wire Lead List #116011 N/A: 116009, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Fabrication, IC, Memory Controller #116012 N/A: 116009, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Fabrication, PAL, P_RAM Priority #116013 N/A: 116063, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Fabrication, PAL, Handshake #116014 N/A: 116063, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Netlist-Proto 1, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Netlist-Proto 2, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Fabrication, PAL, P_RAM strobes #116015 N/A: 116066, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fabrication, PAL, slice processor, input, output #116016 N/A: 116090, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Fabrication, PAL, [various] #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Fabrication, PAL, [various] #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Schematics, [various] #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Fabrication, PAL, [various] #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Fabrication, [various] #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Assembly, DMA #1160-- N/A: 116008, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Fabrication, DMA, ROM #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Schematics, ROM module #116058 N/A: 116057, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - CPU Support #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - P_RAM Mux #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - P_RAM #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Data Buffer #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Schematics, Host Control #116074 N/A: 116072, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Video Count #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Print Count #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - D-RAM Control #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Map / Mux #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - D-RAM #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Slice IP #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Printer Register #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Clock Generator #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Video Output #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Fabrication, PAL, DMA #1160-- N/A: 1160--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - I/O Driver #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - D-Ram #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Address Mux #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Video [various] #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Fabrication, PAL, Print [various] #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - P-RAM Control B #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Fabrication, PAL, [various] #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Video Buffer #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Fabrication, PAL [various] #1161-- N/A: 1161--, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - 32 bit Interface Documents, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - ASIC [miscellaneous], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Schematics [miscellaneous], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Upstart Corporate, 1987 - 1988 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Upstart: Product Spec, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Quintar (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Upstart/Colorblind Premium Gift (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Colorblind Ron Jones, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Upstart Corporation Market Research, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Upstart Corporation Dealer Program, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Upstart/Colorblind Competitors, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Upstart Corporation Catalog Program, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Upstart/Colorblind Production Quotes, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Colorblind-Technical/Development (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Upstart/Colorblind Financial (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Upstart/Colorblind Advertising, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Colorblind/XOR Corp, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Colorblind Financial, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Upstart Corporation, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Upstart Board Meetings, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Series 8: Accession 2017-243
  This series compromises the 2017 addenda to the original Lee Felsenstein papers as accessioned in 2004.
  - Subseries 8.1: Contracting & Consulting Work
    Felsenstein regularly performed consulting and contract work as 'Golemics, Inc.', a corporation of which he was the sole employee, and later as 'Fonly, LLC'. As such, all ‘Golemics’- and 'Fonly'-branded work has been consolidated in this subseries with any other contracting and consulting work Felsenstein performed. Records are organized by 'Job' number, and secondarily by order processed.
    - 141000 Palmbox Top Assy. (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Job 141 - Board Files (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - 141007 Fab, Palmbox Analog Circuit Board (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - 141011 Software, Palmbox PIC (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - 141012 Fab, Palmbox End Panels (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - 141013 Schem., Palm Box Cover (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - 141014 Fab, Palmbox Housing (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Job 142 - Vendors (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Job 142 - Deliverables (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - 143004 Schematic, PCB, Multiplexer, Grid (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - 143014 & 143011 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - 143017 Fab, PCB, Electrode, Grid (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - 143024 Schematics - O.S.C. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Job 145 - Spec (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Job 145 - OS (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Job 145 - Flash/Eprom (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Job 145 - LCD Panels (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Job 145 - LCD Controllers (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Job 145 - Security Architecture (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Job 145 - Network PCI Cards (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Job 145 - USB Controllers (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Job 145 - CPU Data Shows (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Job 145 - Character Recognition (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Job 145 - Smart Card (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Job 145 - NEC VR412x, 417x (Box 46, Folder 1)